Becky Bush

beckybush67@gmail.com

Canada, Manseau QC

Summary

Full stack developer with over 8+ years of experience in Java/JS, Angular, Vue, React, Python, Node.js. In improving user engagement by 15%, reducing development and deployment time by 20% and mentoring junior developers, resulting in a 10% improvement in team satisfaction scores. I have also good experiences of teamwork.

Experience

Remote HubSpot

Connects everything scaling companies need to deliver a best-in-class customer experience into one place.

- Developed membership, event, and legal platform technology solutions, and automated internal processes.
- Generated \$50K+ in annual ad revenue as a system administrator of a large network of websites.
- Developed a node.js server to validate membership and track digital badges being used, saving the company \$22.5K.
- Mentored 6 team members, enabling them to achieve professional growth and personal goals

Los Angeles, BlueTech Software California

Team Leader 2019 - 2020

- Blue Tech provides leading Information Technology products and services for both everyday operations and mission-critical systems. • Researched and created a new application to be used by the company, resulting in a 1.3x increase in sales
- · Created a new software development framework to develop applications faster and more efficiently
- Developed the process of testing and recording the results of the test, thereby increasing the number of tests completed per day by 10%
- Developed a new technique for reducing the time it takes to fix crashes by 20%

Senior Full Stack Developer

Los Angeles, Mezzanine California 2018 - 2019 Full Stack Developer

Mezzanine is a brand experience agency that specializes in creating and executing live and digital experiences for their clients.

- · Developed a collaborative environment for all team members, creating a strong sense of community and empowerment
- Designed a new web application to increase collaboration among design, engineering and sales teams, resulting in a 10% increase in revenue in one quarter
- Built a custom web application for a major client, successfully delivering an integrated CRM system in just 2 weeks
- · Used Adobe InDesign to design, edit and layout the company's print & digital collateral

Geeks 4 Nerds California Junior Web Developer

They may specialize in a wide range of services such as web development, mobile app development, software engineering, IT consulting, and

- · Designed and implemented a new cloud-based mobile POS platform, resulting in a 50% increase in customer retention
- Collaborated with hardware and software development teams to ensure seamless integration of the new POS system
- Continued to develop specialty skills related to his expertise in mobile POS and payment technologies
- Developed and continuously improved an internal knowledge base of best practices for software development

EDUCATION

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology-Hong Kong **Bachelor of Computer Science**

2010 - 2015

Skills

Web: MERN JavaScript HTML CSS Django

Application: C++ · Java Python MATLAB

Database: SQL ·Oracle Mongo dB

more.

Los Angeles,

2015 - 2018

2020 - 2023